{
    "id": "0dc736511531455bb6ab8071b075307a",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "'I haven't turned in the assignment ‘………………………….. have I.’",
            "description": "After a negative remark, we can add another negative remark to it with neither or nor. ",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Neither",
                "Nor"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3bd8f52fcc2c4cdabd86aec40f0eb76f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ........................... cute.",
            "description": "We do not use so much to modify adjectives and adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "so",
                "so much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b9ac6af8de2849aca62b9d32d477cbd1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She worked hard so that she ................................. more.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will earn",
                "might earn",
                "can earn"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "060ca19b1a9841c1b4684170690a317c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for ........................... two hours and then I went home.",
            "description": "We can use another with plural expressions of quantity.",
            "answers": [
                "an other",
                "another",
                "other"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c71c0c5e185d45808a0ce18a13198375"
        },
        {
            "question": "I call my mother ..............................",
            "description": "Everyday means ordinary or typical. Every day means each day.",
            "answers": [
                "everyday",
                "every day",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bbe69a7c0bcf4ac4ac2b4d99fe5aed25"
        },
        {
            "question": "My ………………………………  too heavy.",
            "description": "Luggage does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "luggage is",
                "luggage are",
                "luggages are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "45cda7558a77498b967cac240eaa399e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Either Sam or Peter .............................. to bring the violin.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb when two singular nouns are connected by either/or. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "12c46933069440438e5cc388de6f67e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would rather you .................................... talking to her.",
            "description": "Use a past tense after would rather to refer to the future. ",
            "answers": [
                "stop",
                "stopped",
                "will stop"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f217f20040324e3b98960d9d8c93a179"
        },
        {
            "question": "At least 10 people ................................... in the explosion.",
            "description": "A passive verb is required here. ",
            "answers": [
                "have killed",
                "had killed",
                "have been killed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f2708c62f0ca400fbeca7dfa1058edb3"
        },
        {
            "question": "A number of people .................................. to migrate.",
            "description": "Use a plural verb after a number of use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wants",
                "are wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7be42a8d24ad4d848d5077191e4228ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of people who want to migrate ................................. on the rise.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after the number of.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "06346273ee0b4758b1ad2e04f658854e"
        }
    ]
}